Harshit Dandriyal

Software Engineer

Expert in advanced development methodologies, tools and processes contributing to the design and roll-out of cutting-edge software applications, Also Known for excellent troubleshooting skills – able to analyze code and engineer well-researched, cost-effective and responsive solutions.

dandriyalh9318@gmail.com

9318400300

New Delhi, India

•

linkedin.com/in/harshit-dandriyal-98866419a

github.com/Harshit-Dandriyal

WORK EXPERIENCE

CNCF InternCNCF

09/2022 - 10/2022 Remote(Global)(with Stipend) Meshmap- Figma of devops

TechStack- React.js , cytoscape.js ,Graphql ,Golang,MUI

- worked on visualizing and analyzing large networks of Kubernetes and service mesh deployment using cytoscape.js.
- worked on SVG system rendering design of each node of Kubernetes and service meshes(Istio, Linkerd, Cilium..etc).
- Built custom components with Material-UI, and React packages including custom plug-ins and filters.

Intern at Layer5 Layer5

04/2022 - 09/2022 Remote(Austin, USA) (with Stipend)
Layer5 - Industry-leading cloud native management

TechStack- React.js , Gats-by ,Graphql , MUI, SCSS

- Resolved 50+ bugs in the user interface in Layer5 projects with new innovative ideas and discussions with developers.
- Connected with other Contributors and organizers in weekly meetings, supported brainstorming and idea generation.
- Created dark mode feature for the main website of Layer5,
 Used certified google material design methodologies for designing each component.

Web Developer

Segura Luggage Storage Service

11/2019 - 04/2020

Delhi, India(Startup esops)

Achievements/Tasks

- Developed and structured feature-rich client websites, ensuring that all needs were met and company policies.
- Collaborated with project managers and creative teams to deliver original, efficient solutions with good quality code.
- Participated in weekly meetings with executives, and supported brainstorming and idea generation.

EDUCATION

B.Tech in Computer Science

Maharaja Agrasen Institute Of Technology

08/2018 - 08/2022 Gpa-8.23

12th Boards

Kendriya Vidyalaya Pitampura

05/2017 - 05/2018 86.5% in CBSE Boards

SKILLS

Web Development React NodeJs Golang

Data Structure and Algorithm Docker

Kubernates Service Meshes Git Javascript

PERSONAL PROJECTS

The Gaming Store

- A full stack App(MERN Stack) using firebase with handling online payments with Stripe API.
- Technologies- Redux, Hooks, GraphQL, Stripe, Firebase.
- Considered material designing for UX to give a website a more friendly and gaming-type RGB look.

Automated Code Generation for Testing of React-UI.

- Main tech stack- [ReactJS, Jest, Enzyme, NodeJS, Warnings]
- A tool that automatically generates the test code, inspecting the react component and creating the test suite dynamically.
- Examines the component lifecycle as well as adds edge cases to the addition.

Safe Surfing Modal.

- Real time fake news detection [Accuracy-98%]
- The main tech stacks are Scikit-learn, NumPy, and SciPy, LIAR-plus dataset is used for testing, training, and validation.
- Cookie Monitoring to detect harmful storage and save from any web attack.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Conducted 5 Workshops (09/2019 - 08/2022)

- Workshop on Git, Introduction of OpenSource, React Basics, Service Meshes, docker, Kubernates

Chess Regional Player (06/2016)

-Selected as a Regional level Chess Player.

Competetive Programming (10/2020 - 04/2022)

-5 star in hackerRank Problem Solving.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

JavaScript

Node I

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Chess | 1

Music

Mathematics